<contributors>
    <contributor>
        <author-name> Alex Bleasdale</author-name>
        <bio> Alex has been building web sites and applications for 10 years. During that time he's
            taught MA and BA courses at the University of Sussex, worked as a developer for two
            creative agencies in London (Bates Dorland and Tribal DDB), for 4 years at the BBC as a
            developer and has been living in Minneapolis for the past 2 years. He worked for
            Minnesota Department of Revenue on a project that was modeled on the XRX architecture
            and currently works as a developer for OLSON in Minneapolis. </bio>
        <location>Minneapolis, MN</location>
    </contributor>

    <contributor>
        <author-name> Arun Batchu</author-name>
        <bio> Need a real bio for Arun....but till then... Arun is a software developer in living in
            Minneapolis. He is an expert on all phases of software development and Agile
            methodologies. He is interested in Wiki and the creation of deep RESTful interfaces. </bio>
        <location>Eden Prairie, MN, USA</location>
    </contributor>

    <contributor>
        <author-name> Kurt Cagle</author-name>
        <bio> Need a real bio for Kurt....but till then... Kurt Cagle is the Managing Editor for
            xml.com, part of the O'Reilly Networks. He also write a blog dedicated to XRX issues
            called the Metaphorical Web. He has written extensively on XML topics. </bio>
        <location>Vancover, BC, CA</location>
    </contributor>

    <contributor>
        <author-name> Dan McCreary</author-name>
        <image-url></image-url>
        <bio> Dan is a enterprise data architect and strategist living in Minneapolis. He has worked
            for organizations such as Bell Labs and Steve Job's NeXT Computer as well as founding
            his own consulting firm of over 75 people. He has a background in object-oriented
            programming and declarative XML languages (XSLT, XML Schema design, XForms, XQuery, RDF
            and OWL). He has published articles on various technology topics including the semantic
            web, metadata registries, enterprise integration strategies, XForms and XQuery. He was
            the primary author of the author of the XForms Tutorial and Cookbook and the XRX
            Wikibook. </bio>
        <location>St. Louis Park, MN, USA</location>
    </contributor>

    <contributor>
        <author-name> Joe Wicentowski</author-name>
        <bio> Joe is a historian at the U.S. Department of State who researches the history of U.S.
            foreign relations. He is an example of how XRX can empower non-programmer, content
            experts to take control of their own information. He came to XRX when he discovered that
            (1) XML was an ideal format for publishing his office's richly annotated historical
            content, and (2) XQuery was simple to learn and allowed 'content experts' like him to
            take total and fine-grained control over displaying, querying, and re-purposing their
            growing body of XML content stored in native XML databases. Furthermore, XRX has allowed
            him and his colleagues to design new tools to manage their workflow, mine their content
            for research, and give the public new ways to explore their history online. </bio>
        <location>Washington, DC, USA</location>
    </contributor>

    <contributor>
        <author-name> Chris Wallace</author-name>
        <bio> Need a real bio for Chris....but till then... Chris is a Senior Lecturer at the School
            of Information Systems at the University of the West of England in Bristol, UK. Chris
            has been an active instructor in XML topics for many years and is one of the primary
            authors of the XQuery wikibook. Chris is interested in XQuery, RDF and the semantic web. </bio>
        <location>Bristol, UK</location>
    </contributor>
</contributors>
